hey everyone thanks for listening to The
Grow Your Life podcast my name is
Jeremiah grakowski and this podcast I
help coaches and mentors make more money
and get more clients in their business
my top priority for you is to help you
become a multi-six figure earning coach
and Beyond so that you can make seven
figures I have no desire for anybody who
plugs in with me to stay broke and I'm
on a mission to make you wealthy to make
you rich once you make enough money I'd
love to see you invest that money and
grow it in the stock market be sure to
check out some of the trainings that my
mom Sandy Krakowski has on stock market
investing as you grow your business
income taking that money and then
investing it and growing it imagine
having a one hundred thousand dollar
Investment Portfolio how that would
change your life and the way that you
would look at the world around you it's
possible
and you can do it and I think anybody
can do it I think it's actually a great
compliment to what we teach in this
program as well in this program on the
grow Your Life podcast and in my client
growth accelerator we help coaches and
mentors attract more clients the number
one thing is launching an offer I want
to tell you this every single coach
trainer and Mentor that's been ever out
there in business
has dealt with the self-doubt and
unbelief of
if they're ready yet to Launch
they have tossed around ideas and felt
stuck because they can't figure out
what's the right
strategy to go with right what's the
right path to take
and so realize that you're in good
company because
I've worked with thousands of people
coaches and mentors over the years and
they all deal with this everybody deals
with this and so so understand you're
actually like part of a club
of people that have a a common struggle
is
how do I put an offer together that gets
clients and that allows me to serve
people and make the kind of money that I
want to make and how do I know that it's
good enough to Launch
and my biggest piece of advice is this
is a I would highly recommend you launch
with a group
coaching offer it could be a six or an
eight week
course slash coaching hybrid where
you're teaching a course and you provide
q a coaching for 500 to a thousand
dollars it's one of the best ways for
you to make six figures very quickly
by selling that for five hundred
thousand dollars you sell 20 of them to
make 10 grand if it's 500 bucks you need
to sell only 10 of them to make ten
thousand dollars if it's if it's a
thousand dollars and so that's what I
recommend everybody sell is craft an
offer that you can teach people and
Mentor them and guide them for six weeks
and you don't have to have it completed
before you launch it
you want to pre-sell it you don't want
to finish
the whole thing and have it all done
before you actually put it out there
because you what you'll do is you're
actually going to come up with the
content you'll have the outline figured
out and if you follow the six steps that
we teach in my coaching program
you'll have the outline of what you're
going to teach when you launch the offer
it'll be in your offer copy but you're
going to take what your purchasing
clients are asking you and actually
tweak and adjust and slightly change
about 15 to 20 percent of what you're
going to teach
based off of what people say sometimes
you might throw the whole book out and
realize that the questions that people
are asking are completely different than
what you thought you needed to teach and
you're going to go in that direction in
in my coaching business in all of the
coaching businesses that we've built
that have been successful we've let the
clients Direct
how the coaching interaction goes
by asking basically asking at scale a
group of people what they want to learn
and then teaching to that group of
people exactly what they asked for
and so in a one-on-one coaching setting
you're asking the person what's your
problem what are you struggling with and
I'm going to guide you to find the
answer to that you do the exact same
thing in group coaching you have the
group tell you what they as a group want
to learn and want to grow in that's how
we come up with all of our content
that's how we come up with all of our
coaching
and so you need to actually facilitate a
way to have people tell you what they
want to learn virtual events are the
best way to do this doing online virtual
events launching a live Zoom call
a live Zoom call where people register
and hop on a zoom call with you and you
get to have them tell you what they want
to learn when they register and you even
can do q a and other forms of of
connecting
with those prospects
and leading people
to
get the result that they hoped for get
the result that they're actually wanting
they might say well how do I know I can
lead them to get a result
if you don't know how to do something be
honest about it say I have no clue how
to do this
I've never done this before
I have no experience in doing this
and
that's not in my Lane of what I do one
of the biggest reasons I see that
coaches struggle is they feel the need
to have all the answers because their
group or their clients ask them you know
I've had people for five years ask me on
time management training and to be
honest I I can't articulate how I do
time management it's
it's not really my lane and what I teach
I teach people how to build coaching
businesses and particularly how to get
clients that's my Lane specifically
and so what you want to do is you want
to get people on a zoom call
and then you sell to those people that
paid program that you have
and these are all skill sets that you
can grow in
you're not going to grow in these skill
sets by taking a course by reading a
book
though we do have courses and coaching
on this you're not going to take it by
having a coach
tell you what to do
you actually grow in sales in two ways
this is how you do it you watch somebody
else teach a sales pitch
you watch somebody else who's an expert
who is closing sales teach a sales pitch
in our client growth accelerator
we give you access to all of the virtual
events that we've done so you can
actually watch me close sales every
single virtual event that's closed over
half a million dollars in sales for us
in the last seven months is in there
if you sign up for any of my virtual
events you can watch How I do a sales
pitch
how I close the sale
okay
and then you go out there and do the
same thing with your offer and so you
watch it you pay attention to Mike
Cadence how I structure my language and
we have courses in the members area for
our clients to learn how to do this and
so if you correlate the courses with
watching me do it
with then you actually doing it yourself
and then and real sadly most people are
just
too afraid or prideful
to do a zoom call
if they can't guarantee exactly how it's
going to go and it's going to produce
sales and they know exactly what to say
and I'm sorry but that's a fantasy
you're never gonna that's not gonna
exist that doesn't exist
you want to map out what are you going
to teach people and then you walk people
through that process if you don't know
how to teach people if you don't know
how to guide people you don't know how
to speak publicly those are some skill
sets to grow in is how to actually speak
publicly how to actually open your mouth
how to actually get better at public
speaking it's not anything to be
embarrassed about you get better at it
by doing it more often
by showing up in front of people more
often the reason why I have this podcast
it's not a major
marketing client getter for me I don't
get a lot of my clients through this
podcast
but it helped me grow in my ability to
speak and present and teach
by having to do it once a week
by committing to do it once a week
and so I've gotten better by doing that
you're only going to get better at
teaching presenting and selling by
actually doing the sales pitch there's a
number of trainings out there that
relate to
how do you get good at one-on-one sales
and I'll tell you
sales is more a mindset game than a
strategy game in our courses in the
members area of the client girls
accelerator I I have strategy what do
you say at each stage of your virtual
event and you follow along your topic of
what you're going to teach and literally
you can script It Out by watching that
training in the virtual event Playbook
and then you watch my virtual events and
you see how we follow the same formula
in the six steps to six figures I also
walk you through that in lesson number
five
I'm teaching a live event on Tuesday for
free
called launch your six figure group
coaching offer and I and and I'm
actually going to walk you through that
process in that training
I'm going to walk you through that
process here right now
as well okay so for those of you that
are still listening
when you do a virtual event or a webinar
it's actually very scripted what you're
doing whether you're doing it live or
it's pre-recorded you want it to feel
live and you want people to interact as
if it's live even if it's recording you
want people to think that it's live you
want to post it as a live event you want
to run it as a live event even if you're
playing back a recording okay
and even and when I do that I let people
know that it that it was a recording
but it looks like a live event and it
interacts like one that's how we were
able to automate our business so we
don't have to show up every single day
and so then what do you actually say
during the virtual event the first 33 of
your event is a hundred percent based on
mindset and vision what is the vision
and mindset for the thing that you are
selling to people for the end result or
you might say well this is a free event
why would I tell them the thing after
they that would be the mindset and
vision for when I sell them because they
have to be connected they have to be a
direct shot to each other your virtual
event is a marketing Ploy as a marketing
presentation is basically an infomercial
for the thing you're selling
and so
if you treat it as how you run these
these live Zoom infomercials
is what it is
it's essentially what they are
but they provide a lot of value they're
like they're like they're like infotain
they're like in infotainment edutainment
they're very educational and it's an
edumercial it's sort of like it's a
commercial at the end but there's
there's a lot that they'll learn in
these that's that's
the way that you do them properly is you
actually do provide a lot of value and
information
in these
you can't let your fear of screwing this
up stop you from actually showing up
and you can't let your pride of needing
to do it perfect
and needing it to go perfectly for you
stop you from showing up because you
have your pride so big you need to work
on those two things those are not
serving you they're not serving you in
your business if you're terrified of
things not working out that's something
to grow in
you can't reach a goal by being
terrified of things not working out and
everything is a is an experiment in
business it's all an experiment you're
experimenting to see what works
you're experimenting to see what
actually connects
what people actually resonate with
and so you put an offer out there and
people register and in the live event
the first 33 if you watch all of my Live
Events the first 33 percent
is based off of vision and mindset of
where you are trying to direct people to
think about and this does two things it
repels the people that are judgmental
and that aren't a good fit for you
because they will actually become angry
and disappointed and quit your live Zoom
training because you spent 33 percent of
their time
just reiterating what they signed up for
so do that on purpose do that
intentionally
because then you're going to make sure
that you're talking to the right people
who actually truly have a vision for
where you're going to take them
otherwise you're gonna have a ton of
people that are just gonna ask for their
money back
or they're gonna be angry
and they're just not meant to be your
client anyways then in the middle 33 to
50 percent you can make it bigger or
smaller you go over what is the actual
promised material that I told people
that they were signing up for what was
the actual promised information that
people were registering for
and you give that to people in the
middle portion so you're actually
delivering on what you promised as the
value add for your virtual event I have
a virtual event right now that I'm
running called launcher six figure group
coaching offer in the event I'm walking
people through how to launch a
six-figure group coaching offer
in the beginning portion I talked about
mindset and vision in the middle it's
all about the actual nitty-gritty
actionable steps that they can take
and then in the final
15 to 30 percent you talk about your
sales pitch which is what you have for
sale which is the most logical next step
for them is to join you for this paid
program and if you don't believe that
you can provide value enough to people
to join a program with you then a you
need to get better content you need to
align yourself better with something
that people are going to buy maybe your
Niche might be a topic or an industry
that people don't actually frequently
spend money in if that's the case you
might need to Pivot your Niche just a
little bit
to to align with people who actually
want to buy what you're offering
one of my clients Rick he was originally
marketing to people a market that didn't
want to actually spend money on any of
the things he was marketing so he found
what was a small segment of that market
that does want to spend money
and what it was was he went from just
this overall all Christians how to love
God training
to how
Christians who have written worship
songs can get them listened to by people
so it became more industrialized more
productized more based off of an end
result that that can be a step-by-step
that you can walk people through and
then that's what is sold to them he made
over a million dollars a month doing
that
okay
and so I want you to think about
whatever your thing is
what is the end result that people want
and and the thing that they buy from you
is a painkiller it alleviates the pain
that they have inside that if they
didn't buy it from you they would
continue to experience a certain pain in
their life and they would get it
alleviated by somebody else
and that's what you sell to people in
the very last 33 percent okay and so in
our client growth accelerator we work
with you we Mentor you on on your sales
your funnels your ads your copy getting
more clients and helping you make more
money in your coaching business
so but if you you could literally just
take what I told you in this podcast and
it's gonna unlock you to the next level
get on the waiting list for the client
growth accelerator when we do open the
doors again
you'll be the one of the first to know
when you're on the waiting list it's
worth it it's worth jumping in when we
open the doors we have so many people
right now getting results their life
their lives are being changed from the
client growth accelerator like Judy who
made she now said that she's hitting
almost a high six-figure income monthly
with the training that she's gotten from
the clinical accelerator or like my
client Joshua we started coaching with
him and in one year he was making 140
000 a month in his coaching business
using virtual events like we're talking
about and so even if you just want to
make five thousand dollars a month like
Angie did she spent 500 and made five
thousand or nine thousand dollars in one
month like Emma Dixon
you can learn and and make six figures
all the way up to multiple seven figures
and even eight figures like our client
Rick Pino did like we've done with my
mom Sandy Krakowski
I want to help you and I want you to
become a wealthy coach
you can do it you absolutely can
grow your life everybody